(Sheldon:)Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do.
(Howard:)Can you believe this guy?
(Leonard:)What I don't believe
is you tried to run him over.
(Howard:)Oh, like you've never thought
of doing that.
(Howard:)Don't hate me
just because I lived the dream.
(Sheldon:)Hey, sweet ride.
(Howard:)What are you doing in there?
(Sheldon:)Just breaking in your new car.
Stop that! You stop that!
(Sheldon:)You know what they say.
(Sheldon:)Revenge is a dish best served nude.
- Hey, got a minute?
- Oh, of course, come in.
(Sheldon:)This is an authentic Chinese throwing star,
and I must warn you...
(Sheldon:)...I have seen many people throw them
in movies.
(Raj:)Calm down. Howard has something
he wants to say to you.